地狱犬
Hellhounds!
答对了  迪恩  你的最爱
Yeah, Dean -- your favorite.
不
No!
我不能战斗  不能走
I can't fight. I can't walk.
但我能做一件事
But I can do something.
这里的材料足够做成炸弹
We've got everything we need to build a bomb.
-我们在做什么  - 我们在猎杀鬼魂
- What are we doing? - We're hunting a ghost.
知道什么人才信有鬼吗  疯子
You know who does that? Crazy people!
我们是  疯子
We...are insane.
明天  我们去杀魔鬼
Tomorrow we hunt the devil.
这是我们生命的最后一个夜晚
This is our last night on earth.
拿着它去找路西法  迎面给他一枪
Take this thing to Lucifer and empty it into his face.
你知道我不会伤害你的
You know I'd never hurt you.
狗娘养的混蛋  你给我记着
You listen to me, you son of a bitch.
我会亲手杀了你
I'm gonna kill you myself.
把你的心挖出来
I'm going to rip your heart out!
很好  萨姆
That's good, Sam.
让你心中愤怒的火焰烧得更猛烈些吧
You keep fanning that fire in your belly --
你压抑的愤怒
All that pent-up rage.
我会用得着
I'm gonna need it.
(格伦伍德斯普林斯精神病院)
(凯彻姆市  俄克拉荷马州)
(精神评估  病人:弗莱彻  苏珊  年龄:43  女性  拥有护理资质)
(小男孩清晨惨死在着火的家中)
护士告诉我说
The nurses tell me
你不肯吃药
That, uh, you're not taking your medication.
能告诉我为什么吗
You want to tell me why?
苏珊
Susan?
那药让我犯困
The pills make me sleepy,
但我不能睡觉
But I can't...
我睡了  它就会来
If I sleep, it'll come.
你是说怪物
You mean the monster.
这件事我们已经谈过了
Now, we have talked about this.
它杀了安妮
But it killed Annie.
苏珊  你患了精神分裂症
Susan, you're schizophrenic.
你的精神  会有错乱
Your mind plays...tricks on you.
令你迷惑
You get confused.
有时候你会产生幻视
Sometimes you see things.
我清楚自己的问题
I know what I am.
比如我能看见我死去的儿子站在你身后
Like I can see my dead son standing right behind you --
我知道他不是真的
I know he's not real.
但那怪物是真的
But the monster -- it is real.
安妮曾是你的室友
Annie was your roommate,
发生在她身上的事情
And what happened to her was painful --
我们都很难过
For all of us.
或许想象出一个怪物  会比直面
Perhaps it's easier for you to conjure up a monster
她自杀的惨象  更容易让你接受
than to face how tragic her suicide really was.
夜里我能听到它的嚎叫
I can hear it at night,
就在墙壁里
In the walls.
求你了
Please.
你一定要相信我
You have to believe me.
苏珊
Susan...
世界上没有怪物
There is no such thing as monsters.
十点三十分  熄灯了
It's 10:30  lights out.
我的上帝
Oh, my God!
救救我
Help me!
Help me!!
他们今晚闹得真早
They're starting early tonight.
快来人
Hurry!
它来了
It's coming!
救救我
Help me!!
(病史)
芝加哥有位巴巴医生推荐你们过来的
You were referred to me by a Dr. Babar in Chicago.
是的
That's right.
是不是有本关于大象的童话书
Isn't there a children's book about an elephant
叫做《巴巴家族》的
named Babar?
我不清楚
I don't know.
我没有关于大象的书
I don't have any elephant books.
医生  我想
Look, doctor, I-I think that...
那位医生已经没有办法了
The doc was in over his head with this one
因为我弟弟他
'cause my brother's, uh...
好了  谢谢
Okay, fine. Thank you.
不必了  真的
That's -- that's really not necessary.
说说你现在感觉如何吧  亚历克斯
Why don't you tell me how you're feeling, Alex?
我很好
I'm fine.
我是说  好吧  有一点点不开心  我想
I mean, okay, a little depressed, I guess.
好的  知道原因吗
All right. Any idea why?
可能是因为  我引发了天启
Probably because I started the apocalypse.
天启
The apocalypse?
没错
Yeah, that's right.
你认为是你引发的
And you think you started it.
是的
Well, yeah.
是这样
I-I mean
我杀了一个恶魔  莉莉丝
I killed this demon -- Lilith --
不小心把路西法从地狱放了出来
And I accidentally freed Lucifer from hell.
他在世间横行  我们正在试图阻止他
So, now he's topside, and we're trying to stop him.
你们是指
W-who is?
我  他
Me. And him.
还有一个天使
And, uh, this one angel.
你是说  你的守护天使?
Oh, you mean like a -- like an angel on your shoulder?
不是  他叫卡西迪奥  穿一件风衣
No, no. His name's Castiel. He wears a trench coat.
明白我的意思了吧  医生
See what I mean, doc?
这孩子为这事恼恨自己几个月了
I mean, the kid's been beating himself up about this for months.
天启并不是他的错
The apocalypse wasn't his fault.
不是?
It's not?
不是
No.
还有一个恶魔  叫露比
There was this other demon -- Ruby.
是她害他对恶魔血上了瘾
She got him addicted to demon blood.
到最后  他整瓶整瓶的灌
I mean, near the end, he was practically chugging the stuff.
我弟弟并不邪恶
My brother's not evil.
他只是
He was just...
偏激
High.
懂了吗
Yeah?
所以  能麻烦您尽快治好他  好让咱哥俩
So, could you fix him up so we can get back
可以重回游走全国灭鬼杀灵的生活吗
to traveling around the country and hunting monsters?
艾玛
Erma...
取消我的午餐时间
Cancel my lunch.
富勒医生希望你俩都留院
Dr. Fuller would like to keep you both under observation
观察几日
for a couple of days.
咱俩  我也留吗
Both? Me too?
是的  宝贝  医生认为这样最好不过了
Yes, sugar. The doctor thinks that would be best.
好了  我要为你做个简单的体检
All right. I'm just gonna give you a little checkup.
行了  拉契特护士  就别拐弯抹角了
All right, look, nurse Ratched, let's get one thing straight --
我可是看过《飞越疯人院》的
I've seen "Cuckoo's nest," So don't try
别和我说精神分析那套狗屁
any of that soul-crushing authoritarian crap on me.
好吧  好吧
Okeydokey.
好了  下一项了  把裤子脱了吧
All right, you can go ahead and take down your pants.
等一下
Wait. Mm.
什么  为  为什么啊
What? What -- what for?
"净身"浴的感觉如何
How was your silkwood shower?
挺好
Okay.
是的  很好  很好
Yeah. Good. Yeah.
很好  水压恰到好处
Good, um... good water pressure.
那个护士
Did the nurse --
非常地周到
She was very thorough.
同意  同意  很周到  很彻底  同意
Yeah. Yeah. Good. Good. Yeah.
真不敢相信我竟然被你说服了来这儿
I can't believe I let you talk me into this.
这是我们应该做的
Hey, it's the least we could do.
马丁救了老爸的次数我们数都数不过来
Martin saved dad's ass more times than we can count.
他是个了不起的猎人
He's a great hunter.
曾经是  直到阿尔伯克基那事为止
Was. Until Albuquerque.
再说我只是希望能有点儿事忙忙  仅此而已
Besides, I-I just figure it's best we keep busy. That's all.
为啥要忙
Better than what?
没什么
Nothing.
好吧  听着
Okay, look -- um...
前几周  你让我感到担心
last few weeks, you kind of been worrying me.
拜托了  萨姆  别再说了
Oh, come on, sam. Stop.
行了  别以为我们进了精神病院
Look, just because we're in the looney bin
你就真可以拿我当疯子看了
doesn't give you the right to head-shrink me.
迪恩  艾伦和乔的死
Dean. Ellen and Jo dying --
没错  这确实非常悲惨  我承认
Yeah, it was a freakin' tragedy, okay?
但我绝不会就此意志消沉的
But I'm not gonna wallow in it.
迪恩  你就是一直在消沉
Dean, you always do this.
你不能再这么下去了
You can't just keep this crap in.
走着瞧吧
Watch me.
噢  他在那儿呢
Oh, there he is.
萨姆  迪恩
Sam. Dean.
哇哦  你俩都长这么大了
Wow, you boys got big.
看起来不错啊
You look good.
谢谢称赞  你也不错  马丁
Thanks. You do, too, martin.
对了  谢谢你们能来
Well, thanks for coming.
如果是当年
In the old days,
就是两只手被绑在身后
I could've taken care of this thing
我也能解决了这怪物
with both hands t-tied behind my back.
只不过
But
现在
well, now...
你认为我们这次的猎杀目标是什么
what do you think it is that we're hunting?
我也完全摸不着头脑
I don't know yet.
鬼魂  恶魔  怪物
A ghost, demon, monster.
动物  植物也或是矿物质东西
Animal, vegetable, mineral.
医院在过去的四个月里出了五起命案
Hospital's had five deaths in the last four months.
医生们全都认定为自杀
Doctors keep calling it suicides,
但他们错了
But they're wrong.
那你见过这怪物吗
So you've seen this thing?
其他人看见过吗
Has anyone seen this thing?
一些病人见过  在眼前闪过
Well, a couple of patients have, uh, had glimpses,
都见得的很少
but that's not a lot to go on.
他们可信吗
Are they reliable?
当然  为什么不可信
Oh, sure. Why wouldn't they be?
天哪  我也说不清
Gee, I don't know.
我知道在你们眼里我是个老废物了
I know you boys think I'm a bag of loose screws.
你们想的可能没错
Well, you wouldn't be wrong.
但若不是这儿真有怪物
But I wouldn't have called you
我也不会打电话通知你们的
unless there was something here.
我能察觉到它的存在
I can feel it in my gut.
我们相信你
We believe you.
那你有检查过那些尸体吗  有发现受攻击的迹象吗
Have you checked any of the bodies, found signs of an attack?
噢  没有
Well, uh, no.
我没法
I don't, uh...
我不能再
I don't go around dead b-bo...
再靠近尸体了
b-bodies anymore.
亚历克斯  埃迪
Alex, Eddie.
我很高兴看到你们已经交到了朋友
Well, I'm glad to see you're making friends.
不如你们和奎恩先生一起加入我们的小组吧
Why don't you and Mr. Creaser join us for group?
拜托了  这边走
Please. Right this way.
其实  我打算让你
Actually, I'm going to be putting you
参加下午的那个组
in the afternoon group.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
坦白地说
Well, to be frank, uh,
你和你弟弟互相依赖的关系
the relationship that you have with your brother
看起来很危险
seems dangerously codependent.
我认为适度的分开对你俩都好
I think a little time apart will do you both good.
好了  谁想最先发言呢
All right, so, who would like to start us off?
还有其他人吗
Anyone else?
好吧  泰德  冷静
All right, Ted. Calm down.
我很冷静
I am calm.
我相当冷静地
and I'd very calmly
谈论猎杀我们的那个怪物
Like to talk about the monster that's hunting us.
泰德  我们不再讨论那个话题
Ted, we're not going to have that discussion again.
对小组没有好处
It's not good for group.
我同意
I agree.
你知道什么对小组没好处吧
You know what else isn't good for group?
那怪物会把我们都吃了的
A monster eating all our faces off!
好  很好  谢谢
All right, fine. Thank you.
-其他人要发言吗  - 当它杀死苏珊的时候
- Now, anyone else. - I saw it!
我看见它了
When it killed susan!
-我也看到了  它有很大的钳子  - 不  不对
- I did, too. It had big lobster claws. - No, it didn't!
像外星人  就像《X档案》里的一样
Yeah, and it was an alien, like on "X-files."
不要说了
Stop it!
帮帮忙  听我讲
Stop helping! Listen to me!
我们都要死了
We're all dead!
够了
That's enough!
根本就没怪物
There is no monster.
泰德  你是要我叫护理员来
Now, Ted, do you need me to call the orderlies...
还是规矩点儿
Or can you behave?
我会守规矩的
Behave.
将军
King me!
埃迪
Eddie?
我是埃里卡·卡特赖特医生
I'm dr. Erica Cartwright.
我负责你的病
I've been assigned your case.
你是我的心理医生吗
You're my shrink?
真好  我真幸运
Well, lucky me.
而你是我的多疑加精神分裂
And you're my paranoid schizophrenic
并带有自恋和人格混乱
with narcissistic personality disorder
和宗教精神分裂的病人
and religious psychosis.
我也很好运
Lucky me.
我们可以谈谈吗
Can we talk?
当然
Yes.
我确实有些问题想问你
I've actually got some questions for you.
真巧  我也有些要问你的
What a coincidence. I've got some for you, too.
好  你问我答  克拉丽斯 (出自《沉默的羔羊》)
Well, then, quid pro quo, Clarice.
好的  汉尼拔  我先问
Okay, Hannibal. I'll go first.
你晚上睡几个小时
How many hours a night do you sleep?
几天睡3 4个小时
Three or four every couple of nights.
你能告诉我关于近来这里的自杀事件吗
What can you tell me about the recent suicides in here?
他们很惨
They were tragic.
你注意到有什么奇怪的事情吗
But you haven't noticed anything strange,
比如有没有黑烟  硫磺这些
You know, like, I don't know, black smoke, sulfur?
没有  怎么这么问  什么意思
No. Why? What's that supposed to mean?
有恶魔的迹象
Demon signs.
我猎杀恶魔  怪物  类似这些
I hunt demons, monsters -- that kind of thing.
你每周饮酒多少
How many drinks do you have a week?
有时我设法入睡  所以
Well, I got to sleep sometime, so --
基本不睡觉的时候都在喝
What's seven days 24 times --
50年代中期的某个地方
It's somewhere in the mid-50s.
有没有个地方特别冷
You ever feel any, uh, any cold spots
或者走在医院的时候觉得寒气逼人
or get a chill walking through the hospital?
我记不得了  如果有呢
Not that I can remember. If I had?
它表示有鬼魂在周围
It means there's a ghost around.
好的
Okay.
你上一次和别人长时间交往是什么时候
When was the last time you were in a long-term relationship?
界定一下这个"长期"
Define "Long-term."
超过两个月
More than two months.
从来没有
Never.
病人的报告里有没有比较离奇的事情
Have the patients reported seeing anything weird?
在这里吗  一直都有
In here? All the time.
好的
Right.
那么
So...
让我们来谈谈你的父亲
...let's talk about your father.
迪恩
Dean.
你还好吧
You okay?
我只是《陷入绝境》
I just got "Thraped."
所以  不  我不好
So, no, I am not okay.
-你发现了什么了吗  - 是的
- Tell me you found something. - Yeah.
有人说他见到过什么  找他谈谈
A guy says he saw the creature. We should talk to him.
一个小时后回到这里见面
Want to meet back here in an hour?
是的  最早解决这个怪物
Yeah. The sooner we take care of this thing,
就可以越早离开
The sooner we can get gone.
这个地方让我毛骨悚然
This place gives me the creeps.
你好
Hi.
我叫温蒂
I'm Wendy.
这地方也不是那么得不好
Maybe this place isn't so bad after all.
哥们
Dude...
你不能那样
You cannot hit that.
泪奔了
Oh, so torn.
是时候了  护士们在巡视
About time. Nurses are on their rounds.
我们有大概15到20分钟  那家伙在哪里
We got, like, 15, 20 minutes. Where is this guy?
306号房
Room 306.
上帝
Oh! Geez!
赶紧  加油  快点
Hurry up! Come on! Hurry up!
退后  迪恩
Hey, back off, Dean!
我发现了些东西
I found something.
-发现了什么  - 在这里
- What do you got? - Right here.
帮我下
Um...give me a hand.
正好
All right.
这个孔穿透了他的脑袋
This hole goes all the way through to his brain.
这意味着什么
What does that mean?
谜底要我们揭晓了
Let's find out.
你来真的吗
Seriously?
你可以在门口守着
You might want to keep watch.
哥们
Dude!
快来看  他的脑里被吸干了
Look -- his brain's been sucked dry.
很漂亮  有人过来了
That's fascinating. Somebody's coming.
你们俩在这里做什么
What are you boys doing in here?
我就要布丁嘛
Pudding!
好吧  过来  跟我来
All right. Come on, you two.
装疯卖傻才有用
Crazy works.
这是原版的小丑杀人狂吗
Are those original gacys?
那都是我画的
I painted those.
我们还是讨论重点吧
Back on point, please.
-不管那个东西是什么  - 画得不错
- Um so whatever this thing is... - Good.
它啜食人的脑子  直到吸干为止
...i-it slurps your brain -- sucks you dry.
是的  所以看上去像是自杀一样
Yeah, then it makes the deaths look like suicides.
有什么印象吗
Any ideas?
是的
Yeah.
而且很糟糕
A bad one.
这是什么
What is it?
我敢赌一份鸡肉大餐这就是我们要对付的
Well, I bet you a chicken dinner it's what we're up against.
死灵
A wraith.
它们打开你的脑壳  吸食你的脑汁
They crack open skulls and feed on brain juice.
-你以前遇到过吗  - 从来没有
- You ever tangle with one before? - Never.
我也从来都不想遇到它
Never wanted to, neither.
那我们该怎么杀了它
So how do we kill it?
银器
Silver.
你甚至只要拿银器碰下死灵
You so much as touch a wraith with the stuff,
它的皮肤就会裂开
and the skin will crackle.
现在这个是好消息
Now, that's the good news.
坏消息是  它们能伪装成人类
The bad news is... they can pass as humans.
它可以伪装成这里任何一个人
It could be any Peter, Paul, or Mary in the joint.
太棒了  那我们怎么找到它
Fantastic. So how do we find it?
用镜子
A-a mirror.
相传死灵会被镜子照出本相
Lore says a wraith will show its true form in a mirror.
好吧  看来我们得一个一个检查
Okay, well, we just got to spot-check
所有的病人和医院职工都得查
every patient and every staff member.
好的
Okay. Yeah.
但是  它在一家精神病院做什么
But, I mean, what's it doing in a mental hospital?
一家疯人院
A nuthouse --
简直就是个完美的密封食物储藏室啊
It's -- it's -- it's a perfect captive victim pool.
是啊
Sure.
谁会相信一个精神病人
Who -- who's gonna believe a patient
说自己看见了一个怪物呢
when they say they saw a monster?
简直就是个完美的狩猎场
It's the perfect hunting ground.
怎么了  医生
What's up, doc?
你说呢
You tell me.
我在猎杀
Hunting.
这次是一个死灵
A wraith, actually.
它可能是任何人
Could be anybody.
所以  我也可能是个怪物
So... I could be a monster?
不是  你没嫌疑了
No. You're clean.
为什么是你呢
Why you?
什么为什么是我
Why me what?
为什么猎杀怪物的人是你
Why do you have to hunt monsters?
为什么不让别人去做
Why not let someone else do it?
因为我找不到第二个这么蠢的人了
I can't find anybody else that dumb.
其实这是我的工作
It's my job.
总得有人去救别人的小命儿吧
Somebody's got to save people's asses.
你的也包括在内
Yours included.
那么  是不是有什么工作量要求
So, is there a quota?
你必须要救多少人才行
How many people do you have to save?
所有人
All of 'em.
All of them?
你觉得你必须拯救所有人
You think you have to save everyone?
是的  全民运动
Yep. Whole wide world of sports.
你怎么做到
How?
相信我  无论你说什么
Believe me -- whatever you've got,
我都听过更奇怪的
I've heard weirder.
快到世界末日了  你知道吗
It's the end of the world, okay?
我是说  这可是圣经里提到的天启
I mean, it's the damn biblical apocalypse.
而且如果我不阻止它并且救下所有人
And if I don't stop it and save everyone,
就没有人能救我们了  我们都得死
Then no one will, and we all die.
那可真糟啊
That's horrible.
是啊  不用你说
Yeah, tell me about it.
我的意思是  不管什么天启
I mean, apocalypse or no apocalypse,
也不管什么怪物
monsters or no monsters,
你肩上的担子可不轻啊
that's a crushing weight to have on your shoulders.
只要想想六十亿人的生命全都靠你了
To feel like six billion lives depend on you.
天呐
God.
你怎么会情愿每天面对这一切
How do you get up in the morning?
问的好
That's a good question.
你好  埃迪
Hello, Eddie.
医生
Doc.
好了
All right.
我找了三个护士站才找到这些
I had to raid three nurses' stations to get these.
虽然只是镀银的  但应该管用
They're only silver-plated, but they should work.
噢  别别别
Oh, no, no, no.
今天不行  甜心  好了  继续走
Not today, sweetheart. Come on. Keep walking.
我
I --
我现在就想要他
I want him now.
他可比你强壮多了
He's larger.
至少她是个人类(暗指之前恶魔和狼人)
You've had worse.
富勒今晚值班
Fuller is on call tonight,
所以我们得等熄灯后对付他
so we'll have to hit him after lights out.
我们三个都去
All three of us.
什么  不
What? No!
马丁  我们得避过保安
Martin, we got to get past the security,
还有护工
past the orderlies,
然后切开那个怪物的喉咙  知道吗
and then cut the boss man's throat, okay?
确实从头至尾都会很糟
It's gonna suck start to finish,
但是我们真的需要支援
but we could use the backup.
不  我做不到
No, I can't.
我做不到
I can't.
我们知道在阿尔伯克基发生了什么
We know what happened in Albuquerque.
你根本不了解
You don't know the half of it.
天呐  我以前就像你们俩一样
God...I used to be just like you two.
我以前一直以为自己是不可战胜的
I used to think I was invincible.
但是后来
And then...
我发现我并不是
Well, I found out I'm not.
马丁  你依旧是个猎人
Martin. You are still a hunter.
不  我不是
No, I'm not!
我很没用
I'm useless!
你们觉得我干吗去调查加州旅馆
Why you think I checked myself into the hotel California?
我本该尽我所能的帮助你们
I'd give anything to help you boys.
我很想那样做
I would.
但是  我做不到
But I-I can't.
抱歉  我做不到
I'm sorry. I can't.
他还在大楼里
He's still in the building.
你去西面找  我看看东面
You take the west wing. I'll take the east.
不  不
No! No!
看他的胳膊
Look at his arm!
伤口没有燃烧
The cut's not burning!
不是他
It's not him!
他不是死灵
It's not him.
你还好吗
You okay?
不
No.
我一点都不好
No, I'm not okay.
我...我...我
I...I...I...
我感觉
I am...
爽呆了
Awesome!
他们给你打针了
They give you something?
是的
Oh, yeah.
他们  该不该打的都打了
They -- they gave me everything.
那...
It...
那简直是太让人激  动了
It's spectacu...lacular.
你一直是个快乐的小醉汉
You always were a happy drunk.
迪恩
Dean...
那个医生不是死灵
The doctor wasn't a wraith.
我知道
I know.
我不知道为什么
I don't understand it.
我是说  我当时在镜子里面看到的
I mean, I saw it in the mirror.
那不是人类
It wasn't human.
或者是你幻视了
Or you're seeing things.
或...或...或许你真的要疯了
Maybe -- m-maybe -- maybe you're going crazy.
我可没疯
I'm not crazy.
得了吧
Well, come on.
我觉得  你已经  半疯好一阵子了
I mean, you've been at least... half crazy for a long time.
自从你从地狱回来
Since you got back from hell --
甚至可能在那之前
Or since before that, even.
我们...我们身在精神病院
And we're in a -- we're in a mental hospital.
没准  你到头来真的疯了
Ma-maybe -- maybe you finally cracked.
你知道  或许
You know, maybe --
或许现在是真正的  彻底的疯掉了
Maybe now you are really, for-real crazy.
我弄错了  就是这样
I made a mistake. That's all.
我会找到那死灵的
I'll find the thing.
好的  我知道
Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I know. I know.
没事的
It's okay. Hey.
看着我
Hey, look at me.
没关系的
It's okay...
因为你是我哥哥
'cause you're my brother...
我会永远爱你的
And I still love ya.
啵
Boop.
你今天没来参加我们的谈话治疗
You missed our session today.
我有点儿忙
I'm a little busy.
还在猎杀那个死灵吗
Still hunting that wraith?
人们正在死去
People are dying.
总会有人死的
People die all the time.
小姐  你干吗
Look, lady, why don't you
非得管我猎鬼的事
just let me do my job,
没准我还能救你一命呢
maybe save your life?
我担心的可不是自己的命
It's not my life that I'm worried about.
我的天  我很好  明白吗
Oh, my go-- I am fine, okay?
我很好
I'm fine.
得了吧  就算你不信
Come on. Even you don't believe that.
你将自己置身于这么大的压力之下
All this pressure that you're putting yourself under,
所有这些自责  这会要你的命的
all this guilt -- it's killing you.
你没法拯救所有人
You can't save everybody.
你做不到
You can't.
这些天你根本没能救到任何人  迪恩
Hell, these days, you can't save anybody, Dean.
-你说什么  - 我说的是事实  迪恩
- What'd you say?  - The truth, Dean.
艾伦和乔是因为你死的
You got Ellen and Jo killed.
你朝路西法开枪  却没法干掉他
You shot Lucifer, but you couldn't gank him.
你阻止不了萨姆去杀莉莉丝
You couldn't stop Sam from killing Lilith,
对了  你还打破了第一道封印
And, oh, yeah, you broke the first seal.
你做的一切都是失败的
All you do is fail.
你真的觉得你  迪恩·温彻斯特
Did you really think that you, Dean Winchester,
就凭借普通教育水平和一种无所谓的态度
with a G.E.D. And a give-'em-hell attitude,
就能将恶魔打败
were gonna beat the devil?
省省吧
Please.
这个世界要玩完了
The world is gonna burn,
你对此无能为力
and there is nothing that you can do about it.
你是谁
Who are you?
你是怎么知道这些事情的
How do you know that stuff?!
嘿  冷静点
Hey. Settle down.
告诉我
Tell me!
我叫你冷静
I said settle down.
你难道是
Are you...
她是谁
Who is she?
谁
Who?
你瞎呀  她呗
What are you, blind?! Her!
兄弟  那里没人
Pal, there's nobody there.
我并不存在  迪恩
I'm not real, dean.
我在你的思想里
I'm in your head...
因为你就要疯了
'cause you are going crazy.
离我远点
Just leave me alone.
你想见我
You asked to see me?
是的  谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
我
I, um...
我只是想和你道歉
I just wanted to apologize.
伤了你我深感抱歉
I feel horrible about what I did to you.
我以为你是怪物
I thought you were a monster.
我知道
I know that.
问题是  为什么呢
The question is, why?
我  我当时
I-I was...
原因不重要了
It doesn't matter, um...
因为昨晚的事过后
because after what happened last night,
我终于
I-I had a...
想清楚了
moment of clarity.
我意识到  世上根本就没有怪物这东西
I realized there's no such thing as monsters.
听你这么说  我很欣慰
Well, I'm...glad to hear you say that.
不过说实话
But honestly?
有怪物的幻想对你来说
Monsters are the least
已经是微不足道的问题了
of your problems.
出现幻觉  人们可以学着适应并且生存下去
People can learn to live with delusions,
可你内心的那种愤怒
but the anger I saw in you.
我
I...
你打伤了那两个人  而且你还想杀了我
You hurt those two men, and you were going to kill me.
当你对我穷追不舍的时候
The look in your eyes
你眼中的那种神色
when you came after me --
我
I...
就好像  你已经丧失人性了
It was like you were barely even human.
像是被附身了一样
Like a man possessed.
我知道
I know.
拜托
Please...
只是
just...
你能再给我一次机会吗
Could you give me a second chance?
这又不是在监狱里
Well, this isn't a prison.
你可以去公共休息室
You'll be allowed to go to the day room.
不过要有人监督
Under supervision.
谢谢
Thank you.
不过如果你再像那样爆发的话
But if there is one more outburst,
我就把你转到特殊病患区
I will transfer you to a facility
他们有专门对付暴力倾向病人的设施
that's equipped to handle violent patients.
相信我  他们绝不会心慈手软的
And believe me, they will be far, far less forgiving.
- 迪恩  - 嘿
- Dean. - Hey.
你怎么了
Whoa. What's wrong?
不是恶魔之血的问题  萨姆
It's not the demon blood, sam.
从来就不是
It never was.
什么
What?
有问题的是你
The problem was you.
一直都是你的问题
It was always you --
你说的谎  你的自负
The lies, your arrogance,
还有你心里的阴暗面
that black spot on your soul.
拜你所赐  我们都快死了
Now we're all gonna die because of you.
-是你一手造成的  - 你害了我们所有人
- It's all your fault! - You killed all of us!
你个可怜的怪物
Pathetic freak!
你个心术不正的混蛋
You evil son of a bitch!
窝囊废
Loser!
-我们全玩儿完了  - 怪物
- We're all gonna die! - Freak!
窝囊废
Loser!
怪物
Freak!
离我远点儿
Leave me alone!
别碰我
Leave me alone!!
滚开  别碰我
Leave me alone! No!
别碰我  离我远点儿
Stop it! Leave me alone!
别碰我  不是我的错
Leave me alone! I didn't do it!
放开我  别碰我
Get off of me! Leave me alone!
不要
No!
别碰我
Leave me alone!
到底怎么了
What's happening?
到底怎么回事儿
马丁  马丁  是我  迪恩
Martin, Martin, it's me! It's Dean!
抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
你看起来糟透了  孩子
You -- you look like hell, boy.
确实遭透了
I feel -- ike feel lit, too.
萨姆呢
Where's Sam?
关禁闭
Lockdown.
感谢上帝  他都发疯了
He went crazy, thank god.
什么
What?
我也要疯了
I'm going crazy, too.
我出现幻觉  还有幻听
I'm seeing things. I'm hearing things.
我们俩都是
W-we both are.
疯狂就是线索
Crazy's the clue.
什么意思
W-what do you mean?
-迪恩  - 疯狂就是线索
- Dean? - Crazy's the clue.
你说过了  到底什么
Y-you said that. What?
我是说  我和萨姆的所作所为
I mean, the things that me and Sam have done,
还有我们看见的那些东西
the -- the stuff we've seen --
我俩最后都会变成失心疯了
We're gonna end up going guano eventually,
也许是一对口水横流的小疯子
probably end up like a couple of drooling nutbags.
无冒犯之意
No offense.
没关系
None taken.
可是  我俩在同一天一块发疯了
But me and him freaking out on the same day?
我是说  这应该
I mean, it -- it -- it's got to be the...
-是怪物  - 什么  在哪儿呢  哪儿呢
- The monster. - What?! Where? Where?
不是  什么都没有
No, not -- no, there's nothing there.
听着
Look...
如果这东西不仅仅是以疯子为食呢
...what if this thing doesn't just feed on the insane?
如果他可以让人失去心智呢
what if it makes people insane?
有可能吗  看起来靠谱儿吗
Is that possible? Does -- does that seem real?
这个  我本身虽然也不太
Well, I-I'm -- I'm not the most reliable source
靠谱儿
on what is "Real,"
不过听上去  有点道理
But it sounds -- makes sense.
好吧
Okay.
好  所以  我们被传染了
Okay, so -- s-so we got infected.
这东西让我们变得和疯子一样
You know, something shot us up with crazy.
你知道  某种
You know, something...
说不定
Maybe...
说不定是我老爸的鬼魂
maybe it was the ghost of my dad.
不
No.
集中精力对付死灵  迪恩
Focus on the wraith, Dean.
-集中精力  - 好吧  死灵  死灵
- Focus!  - Right, the wraith. The wraith.
好吧  所以是那个死灵
Okay, so the wraith -- the wraith.
是他毒害我们的神经
It -- it poisoned us.
是他
It, um...
可能是通过毒液  通过  触摸
Maybe with venom, you know, by t-- by touch.
或者毒液  要么是唾液
Or -- or -- or venom or, um, saliva.
温蒂
Wendy.
Wendy?
温蒂对我和萨姆一通狂亲
Wendy! Wendy slobbered all over me and Sam!
所以我们才被感染
That's how we got infected!
我可不能踩在砖缝上
I can't step on the cracks.
这是真的吗
Is this real?
当然了  小甜心
Oh, it is, sugar.
千真万确
It's very real.
她还活着
She's still alive!
温蒂的病房里有两个病人
There's two patients in Wendy's room.
他们袭击了我
They attacked me.
迪恩  你能听到吗
Dean? Can you hear me?
迪恩
Dean!
你得追上去杀了那个东西
You've got to get out there and kill that thing.
我来照顾她
I'll take care of her.
我  不行
I-I can't.
你必须去  别无选择  孩子
You have to. You have no choice, son.
快去
Go!
迪恩  快去
Dean, run!
快去
Run!
嘿  放开我
Hey! Let me go!
那可不行
No.
现实世界无法承受你过于强烈的怒火
You are far too angry to be out there in the real world.
-原来是你  - 当然是我
- You!  - Of course it's me.
我不得不说  你们俩还真是辜负师父啊
I got to say, you hunters don't exactly live up to your rep.
我是说  马丁是个废物  毫无威胁
I mean, Martin's a wreck. He's harmless.
而你和你哥跑进来
And you and your brother come in here,
不加掩饰的说猎杀怪物之类的事
talking tough about killing monsters?
这样一来  让你们轻易就暴露了
Kind of made you easy to spot.
我只需要轻轻一碰
Then all it took was a touch...
你就难逃我手心了
...and you were mine.
我爱死这里了
Oh, I love it in here.
这儿简直就像我的私人五星级酒店套房
This place is my own personal five-star restaurant.
疯狂的脑内充满了多巴胺和肾上腺素
Crazy brains -- they get soaked in dopamine and adrenaline
激素与化学反应之间的碰撞
and just all sorts of hormones and chemicals
真是无比美味可口
that make them delicious.
越是疯狂的大脑  越是美味
And the crazier they are, the better they taste.
都是你干的
You did this to me!
我是有推波助澜
Well...I helped.
但这种愤怒
But that rage?
可不关我的事  是你自己的问题
No, no, no, no. That's all you.
我可不会让人发疯  只是火上浇油而已
I don't make crazy. I just crank up what's already there.
这一切都是你咎由自取
You build your own hell.
我只是提供你机会而已
But I give you the legos.
而一旦等到时机成熟
And when you're ripe...
则由我来消除你的痛苦
...I make all of your problems disappear.
你离他远点
You get away from him!
小子  你真以为自己能搞得定吗
Do you really think this is gonna end well for you, kiddo?
没有
No.
但反正我疯了  管他什么呢
But I'm crazy, so what the hell.
你还疯着呢吗
You still crazy?
和平时差不多吧
Not any more than usual.
-我们得快离开这鬼地方  - 没错
- We got to get out of here.  - Yeah.
看来汤姆·克鲁斯说得没错  心理医生烂透了
Well, looks like Tom Cruise was right. Shrinks suck.
你怎么了
What are you doing?
萨姆  你没事吧
Sam, you okay?
有事
No.
-那个死灵  - 怎么了
- No, the wraith.  - What about her?
她说得没错
She was right.
不  反正她死了  行了吧
No, she wasn't. She's dead, okay?
快上路吧  我得喝一杯  或一打
Let's hit the road. I need a drink. Or 12.
虽然大多数时候我能压抑
Most of the time I can hide it,
但是  我的确很愤怒
But...I am angry.
我痛恨所有的一切
I'm mad at everything.
我以前痛恨你和爸爸
I used to be mad at you and dad,
之后是莉莉丝  现在又是路西法
then lilith, now it's lucifer.
我找了借口  归咎于露比和恶魔血统
A-and I make excuses. I blame ruby or the demon blood.
但其实错不在他们  而在于我
But it's not their fault. It's not them. It's me.
在于我的内心
It's inside me.
我一直充满愤怒
I am mad all the time...
我也不知道自己为什么这样
And I don't know why.
好  够了
Okay, stop.
别说了
Stop it.
就算是这样
So what if you are?
你准备怎样  一走了之吗
What are you gonna do, take a leave of absence?
还是要答应路西法的要求
You gonna say yes to Lucifer?
还是怎样
What?
不  当然不是  我
No, of course not. I --
正是如此
Exactly.
这就是你要面对的
And that's exactly what you're gonna do.
你要么被这些包袱压垮
You're gonna take all that crap,
要么就放下包袱  抛开过去
And you're gonna bury it.
忘记所有的一切
You're gonna forget about it...
如此一来我们才能继续前进
Because that's how we keep going.
我们最后才不会像马丁那么落魄
That's how we don't end up like Martin!
你同意吗
Are you with me?
说啊  老弟  你同意吗
Come on, man. Are you with me?
我同意
I'm with you.
很好
Good.
那就他妈的快走吧
Let's get the hell out of here.